huckmagazine.com 2008-07-04

# Huckmagazine.com Privacy Statement | HUCK Magazine - Surf, skate, snow, travel, music, film, art, fashion

**Huck Newsletter**  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [newsletter@huckmagazine.com](mailto:newsletter@huckmagazine.com)

[We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our [newsletter page](http://www.huckmagazine.com/cgi-bin/dada/mail.cgi/list/huckmag/), or you may contact us at +44 (0) 207 7293675, [newsletter@huckmagazine.com](mailto:newsletter@huckmagazine.com) or Studio 209, Curtain House, 134-146 Curtain Road, London, EC2A 3AR to opt-out.]

We will never pass your name or email address on to any third parties.

**Competitions**  
We may provide you the opportunity to participate in competitions our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and postal address), and demographic information (such as postcode).

We use this information notify competition winners and send out prizes.

We use [may use] a third party service provider to send out the prizes for these competitions; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a competition with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

**Log Files**  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyse trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

We use a third-party tracking service called Google Analytics that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp. We use this information to better gain an understanding about how our site is used by visitors, helping us to update and improve the web site.

**Links to Other Sites**  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Huck Ltd. Please be aware that we, Huck Ltd, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

**  
Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Huck Magazine Ltd.  
Studio 209, Curtain House,  
134-146 Curtain Road,  
London,  
EC2A 3AR

+44 (0) 207 7293675
